export const data = [
  {
    pregunta: "6 x 4 = ?",
    opcion1: "27",
    opcion2: "24",
    opcion3: "34",
    respuesta: "24",
    preguntaNumero: "1/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "9 x 6 = ?",
    opcion1: "64",
    opcion2: "52",
    opcion3: "54",
    respuesta: "54",
    preguntaNumero: "2/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "7 x 6 = ?",
    opcion1: "42",
    opcion2: "46",
    opcion3: "40",
    respuesta: "42",
    preguntaNumero: "3/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "3 x 8 = ?",
    opcion1: "27",
    opcion2: "24",
    opcion3: "34",
    respuesta: "24",
    preguntaNumero: "4/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "9 x 8 = ?",
    opcion1: "62",
    opcion2: "63",
    opcion3: "72",
    respuesta: "72",
    preguntaNumero: "5/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "6 x 8 = ?",
    opcion1: "48",
    opcion2: "58",
    opcion3: "72",
    respuesta: "48",
    preguntaNumero: "6/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "3 x 9 = ?",
    opcion1: "32",
    opcion2: "36",
    opcion3: "27",
    respuesta: "27",
    preguntaNumero: "7/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "4 x 8 = ?",
    opcion1: "30",
    opcion2: "32",
    opcion3: "36",
    respuesta: "32",
    preguntaNumero: "8/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "5 x 9 = ?",
    opcion1: "40",
    opcion2: "35",
    opcion3: "45",
    respuesta: "45",
    preguntaNumero: "9/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "2 x 8 = ?",
    opcion1: "16",
    opcion2: "14",
    opcion3: "18",
    respuesta: "16",
    preguntaNumero: "10/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "7 x 5 = ?",
    opcion1: "32",
    opcion2: "40",
    opcion3: "35",
    respuesta: "35",
    preguntaNumero: "11/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "6 x 9 = ?",
    opcion1: "50",
    opcion2: "54",
    opcion3: "64",
    respuesta: "54",
    preguntaNumero: "12/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "9 x 7 = ?",
    opcion1: "63",
    opcion2: "72",
    opcion3: "66",
    respuesta: "63",
    preguntaNumero: "13/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "6 x 5 = ?",
    opcion1: "30",
    opcion2: "35",
    opcion3: "25",
    respuesta: "30",
    preguntaNumero: "14/15",
  },

  {
    pregunta: "4 x 9 = ?",
    opcion1: "36",
    opcion2: "40",
    opcion3: "32",
    respuesta: "36",
    preguntaNumero: "15/15",
  },
];
